Host but her name is gemita really
Host pero que se llama gemita de verdad
Gema gemita thousand No I would never do that to
Gema gemita mil No yo jamás le haría eso
Auro just kidding Look Auro Hey Auro
Auro fuera coña Mira Auro Oye Auro
listen to the offer I would never do that to
escucha la oferta jamás le haría eso a
aurom never Hey a promise is a
aurom jamás Oye una promesa es una
promise it wouldn't be a
promesa no sería una caza
partner hunt where I know perfectly well that I do
partners donde sé perfectamente que
n't like auron but I'm going to hook up with
auron no me gusta pero me voy a liar con
him to get a little bit of fame and on
él para buscar un poquito de fama y en
Twitter he's gone brainless You think
Twitter ha c descerebrado Tú te crees
I'm going to answer an
que yo me voy a poner a contestarle un
idiot who says that
subnormal que diga que
I'm putting one down when I eat
yo poniendo verde a una cuando yo me
three [ __ ] come on Javi you have to
como tres pollas vamos Javi tienes que
investigate that because the truth is I don't know if I should
investigar eso pues la verdad no sé si
get into such a deep subject Javi
meterme en ese tema tan profundo Javi
verify that but what way could I
verifica eso pero qué forma podría yo
as a journalist have to verify
como periodista tener de de verificar
that information that he just said it's
esa información que acaba de soltar es
his word against the other three
su palabra contra la de los otros tres
No I don't know let's see it has its logic it has
No yo que sé a ver tiene su lógica tiene
its logic it's not like How am I going to hook up
su lógica no es como Cómo me voy a meter
with gemita if I eat three [ __ ]
con gemita si yo me como tres pollas